<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Devean Medium</title>
    <link>https://www.devean.cn/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Devean Medium</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.devean.cn/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Low-Latency, High-Availability, High-Concurrency Trading Service Technical Solution</title>
      <link>https://www.devean.cn/en/blog/2024/qptrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.devean.cn/en/blog/2024/qptrade/</guid>
      <description>Background Current Situation: BTC and ETH simple option orders can only be placed with BTC or ETH, not with the stablecoin USDT. Functional Requirements Users can directly place option orders using USDT stablecoin. After closing options, BTC and ETH are directly exchanged for USDT and transferred to the user&amp;rsquo;s account. Non-Functional Requirements Low latency (dependence on market matching of trading services, higher latency may result in capital loss due to market changes) High availability (service should not be down, upgrade and release should minimize downtime, and automatic complete recovery should be possible after restart) High concurrency (when trading market data arrives, multiple users operate concurrently, and users are concurrent, no queuing for processing) Business Process Users place option orders in USDT mode for BTC simple options.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributed Tracing</title>
      <link>https://www.devean.cn/en/blog/2024/distributed-tracing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.devean.cn/en/blog/2024/distributed-tracing/</guid>
      <description>What is Distributed Tracing？ Distributed tracing, also known as distributed request tracking, is a methodology for analyzing and monitoring distributed service profiles, especially for failures that occur for unknown and degraded performance reasons.&#xA;Core concepts traceId:Identifies a unique ID generated by a single user request spanId:Identifies the position of this call in the call chain Why Distributed Tracking is Needed？ With the growth of business volume, monolithic services have been unable to meet the demand, so SOA servitization and microservices, and multiple instances of each service are deployed, resulting in increased difficulty in troubleshooting and performance issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free CA certification details process</title>
      <link>https://www.devean.cn/en/blog/2023/free-ca-certificate-configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.devean.cn/en/blog/2023/free-ca-certificate-configuration/</guid>
      <description>Nginx Configuration nginx.conf config server { listen 80; listen [::]:80; server_name www.domain.com domain.com; return 301 https://$server_name$request_uri; } # HTTPS server server { listen 443 ssl; listen [::]:443 ssl; server_name www.domain.com domain.com; # website root direction root /usr/share/nginx/domain; index index.html index.htm; # SSL ssl_session_cache shared:SSL:1m; ssl_session_timeout 10m; ssl_ciphers PROFILE=SYSTEM; ssl_protocols TLSv1 TLSv1.1 TLSv1.2 TLSv1.3; ssl_prefer_server_ciphers on; proxy_ssl_server_name on; location / { } error_page 404 /404.html; location = /40x.html { } error_page 500 502 503 504 /50x.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Is Arbitrage</title>
      <link>https://www.devean.cn/en/blog/2023/what-is-arbitrage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 22:59:31 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.devean.cn/en/blog/2023/what-is-arbitrage/</guid>
      <description>This paper briefly introduces what is arbitrage, what are the arbitrage methods and the reasons why arbitrage fails.&#xA;What Is Arbitrage Arbitrage is making a sure profit in excess of the risk-free rate of return. In the language of quantitative finance we can say that an arbitrage opportunity is a portfolio of zero value today which is of positive value in the future with positive probability,and of negative value in the future with zero probability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mathematical Applications in Quantitative Finance</title>
      <link>https://www.devean.cn/en/blog/2023/mathematical-applications-in-quantitative-finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 22:59:31 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.devean.cn/en/blog/2023/mathematical-applications-in-quantitative-finance/</guid>
      <description>This paper volume popularized the application of mathematics in quantitative finance, common modeling methods, and common mathematical tools in quantitative finance.&#xA;What are the different types of Mathematics found in quantitative finance? The field of mathematics most used in quantitative finance are those of probability theory and differential equations. And,of course, numerical methods are usually needed for producing numbers.&#xA;Here‘s a list of the various approaches to modelling and a selection of useful tools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motorcycle Travel Around Xinjiang</title>
      <link>https://www.devean.cn/en/blog/2023/motorcycle-tour-around-xinjiang/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.devean.cn/en/blog/2023/motorcycle-tour-around-xinjiang/</guid>
      <description>Motorcycle Tour Around Xinjiang Copyright: The following pictures are copyrighted by me, all commercial use is prohibited, if you need commercial use, please contact me for authorization, infringement will be punished! 2023.8.2 Beijing &amp;ndash; Bayannaoer Linhe Service Area 2023.8.3 Bayannaoer river service area - Ejin Banner 2023.8.3 Ejin Banner &amp;ndash; Hami 2023.8.5 Hami - Barkol Altun Street Hami Cultural Hall 哈密回王墓 天山庙 巴里坤草原 2023.8.6 巴里坤-吐鲁番-乌鲁木齐 巴里坤糊 天山无人区峡谷 吐峪沟麻扎村 2023.8.7 乌鲁木齐 2023.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://www.devean.cn/en/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.devean.cn/en/page/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
